<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crusblog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Crusblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Heyyy! I&amp;rsquo;m Crus, a tech enthusiast deeply engaged in cybersecurity, machine learning (ML), and AI-driven projects. My primary focus is on applying cutting-edge technologies to real-world problems, particularly through Python programming and interactive website development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a growing expertise in cybersecurity, where I explore defensive strategies, ethical hacking, and securing digital environments. Additionally, I enjoy delving into AI, from creating personalized bots to building many kinds of tools and interactive web platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Heyyy! I&amp;rsquo;m Crus, a tech enthusiast deeply engaged in cybersecurity, machine learning (ML), and AI-driven projects. My primary focus is on applying cutting-edge technologies to real-world problems, particularly through Python programming and interactive website development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a growing expertise in cybersecurity, where I explore defensive strategies, ethical hacking, and securing digital environments. Additionally, I enjoy delving into AI, from creating personalized bots to building many kinds of tools and interactive web platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I have a keen interest in gaming, which inspires some of my creative projects, my core passion lies in sharing my experiences with cybersecurity and AI technologies. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m developing a blog to provide insights into these fields, alongside practical tips for enthusiasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether it’s creating an AI summarization site, enhancing my knowledge of Python, or solving cybersecurity challenges, I’m always excited to tackle new opportunities and share what I learn along the way!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://crusblog.vercel.app&#34;&gt;My Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/CRUSVEDER&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://myportfolio-yash.vercel.app&#34;&gt;portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://crusbpost.vercel.app&#34;&gt;Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Interests:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cybersecurity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machine Learning &amp;amp; AI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Python Programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Game Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gaming Tips &amp;amp; Guides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projects:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spiral Abyss Guide&lt;/strong&gt;: A detailed site for Spiral Abyss strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Summarization Website&lt;/strong&gt;: A project for summarizing documents and interacting with uploaded data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wordle Game Website&lt;/strong&gt;: A custom Wordle game featuring Genshin Impact characters and items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to reach out to me via any of the links above!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my showcase, where I highlight some of my key projects and work in progress. This space is dedicated to demonstrating the skills and technologies I’ve been working on, from web development to AI implementations. Here are a few of the projects I’ve been involved in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projects:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gacha Guide Site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
A comprehensive platform for Spiral Abyss strategies, offering tips and tricks for progressing through the game’s challenging floors. Features detailed guides and character suggestions.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/&#34;&gt;Visit the site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my showcase, where I highlight some of my key projects and work in progress. This space is dedicated to demonstrating the skills and technologies I’ve been working on, from web development to AI implementations. Here are a few of the projects I’ve been involved in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projects:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gacha Guide Site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
A comprehensive platform for Spiral Abyss strategies, offering tips and tricks for progressing through the game’s challenging floors. Features detailed guides and character suggestions.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/&#34;&gt;Visit the site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Summarization Website&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
A tool to upload PDFs, DOC files, and plain text for automatic summarization. It also allows for a Q&amp;amp;A interaction with the uploaded content, making it easy to extract key information.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/&#34;&gt;Explore the AI Summarizer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wordle Game Website - Genshin Impact Edition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
A custom Wordle game tailored to Genshin Impact characters and items. With options for different word lengths, players can challenge themselves with Genshin-related words.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/&#34;&gt;Play Wordle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interactive Portfolio Website&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
An engaging, game-like interactive portfolio showcasing my projects and skills. Visitors can explore various sections, similar to navigating a game world.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;/&#34;&gt;Check out the Portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech Stack:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Programming: Python (Flask, Django, FastAPI), JavaScript, TypeScript ShellScript, Bash, Go&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Development: HTML/CSS, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, React, Next.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Databases: PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Redis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI/ML: TensorFlow, PyTorch, NLP (spaCy, NLTK), OpenCV&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cybersecurity: Wireshark, Metasploit, Burp Suite, Nmap, Aircrack-ng, OpenVAS, Snort, Maltego&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DevOps: Docker, Kubernetes, Git, CI/CD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Testing: Pytest, Postman, OWASP ZAP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Tools: Selenium, Scrapy, AWS, Kali Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with other developers and designers to bring new ideas to life. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in working together, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to contact me!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to explore my work and reach out if you have any questions or suggestions!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. The Ultimate Guide to Elemental Reactions in Genshin Impact</title>
      <link>/posts/blog-2-genshin-elemental-reaction-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog-2-genshin-elemental-reaction-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction-understanding-the-power-of-elemental-reactions&#34;&gt;Introduction: Understanding the Power of Elemental Reactions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mastering elemental reactions is essential for any Genshin Impact player looking to maximize their damage potential. These reactions not only add depth to gameplay but also allow for creative team compositions that can handle even the toughest foes. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover every elemental reaction, explain how to trigger them effectively, provide the formulas for their damage increases, and share insights on the best team combinations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction-understanding-the-power-of-elemental-reactions&#34;&gt;Introduction: Understanding the Power of Elemental Reactions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mastering elemental reactions is essential for any Genshin Impact player looking to maximize their damage potential. These reactions not only add depth to gameplay but also allow for creative team compositions that can handle even the toughest foes. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover every elemental reaction, explain how to trigger them effectively, provide the formulas for their damage increases, and share insights on the best team combinations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;exploring-each-elemental-reaction&#34;&gt;Exploring Each Elemental Reaction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; src=&#34;/images/all%20elem%20react.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;swirl-anemo--cryoelectrohydropyro&#34;&gt;Swirl (Anemo + Cryo/Electro/Hydro/Pyro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swirl is an Anemo-based reaction that spreads an element to nearby enemies, dealing additional damage and creating opportunities for further reactions. To execute Swirl, hit an enemy with an element like Hydro or Pyro and follow up with an Anemo skill, such as Sucrose&amp;rsquo;s or Venti&amp;rsquo;s abilities. The formula for Swirl damage is given by:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG+Elemental Mastery scaling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swirl is perfect for teams that need to spread elemental effects and create reactions across multiple targets. The more Elemental Mastery you have, the stronger the spread, making it ideal for support characters focused on boosting reactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;melt-cryo--pyro--pyro--cryo&#34;&gt;Melt (Cryo + Pyro / Pyro + Cryo)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; src=&#34;/images/meltreact.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melt is a reaction with the highest damage potential, but its effectiveness depends on the order of the elements. Pyro attacks on Cryo enemies increase Pyro DMG by 1.5x, while Cryo attacks on Pyro enemies double the damage (2x). To perform a Melt reaction, use a Cryo attack from a character like Ganyu and then follow up with a Pyro ability from someone like Xiangling or Hu Tao. The formulas for Melt are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pyro + Cryo&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG×1.5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cryo + Pyro&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG×2
Because of the potential for huge damage, Melt is a prime choice for burst damage and high-output teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;vaporize-hydro--pyro--pyro--hydro&#34;&gt;Vaporize (Hydro + Pyro / Pyro + Hydro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vaporize is another high-damage reaction that can be triggered by either Hydro or Pyro. Hydro attacks on Pyro enemies increase Hydro DMG by 1.5x, while Pyro attacks on Hydro enemies double the damage (2x). This reaction is most commonly seen with Hydro characters like Xingqiu or Barbara using their abilities to set up the reaction for a follow-up Pyro attack from Diluc, Hu Tao, or Bennett. The formulas for Vaporize are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hydro + Pyro&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG×1.5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pyro + Hydro&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG×2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vaporize is highly versatile and can lead to substantial damage when paired with a strong Pyro character for the 2x damage boost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;overloaded-electro--pyro&#34;&gt;Overloaded (Electro + Pyro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overloaded creates an explosion that deals Electro DMG to enemies within range. The formula for Overloaded is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG+Electro DMG scaling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To execute Overloaded, use an Electro ability from a character like Lisa or Fischl and follow up with a Pyro skill from Xiangling or Bennett. While Overloaded is great for burst damage, its AoE nature can make it difficult to control in close quarters, so it&amp;rsquo;s best used when you can keep a safe distance from the explosion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;electro-charged-electro--hydro&#34;&gt;Electro-Charged (Electro + Hydro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Electro-Charged is a reaction that deals Electro DMG over time and is triggered when an Electro skill hits an enemy already affected by Hydro. The damage formula for Electro-Charged is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG+Electro scaling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To trigger this reaction, use an Electro attack from Raiden Shogun or Fischl followed by a Hydro attack from Barbara or Xingqiu. Electro-Charged is perfect for sustained damage, providing consistent pressure over the course of the battle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;superconduct-cryo--electro&#34;&gt;Superconduct (Cryo + Electro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Superconduct is a reaction that not only deals Cryo DMG but also reduces the target&amp;rsquo;s physical resistance, making it highly effective for physical damage dealers. The formula for Superconduct is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG+Cryo scaling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To perform Superconduct, use a Cryo attack from Rosaria or Chongyun followed by an Electro skill from Keqing or Fischl. The lowered physical resistance allows DPS characters like Eula or Ayaka to hit much harder with their physical attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;frozen-cryo--hydro&#34;&gt;Frozen (Cryo + Hydro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frozen is a reaction that inflicts the Frozen status on enemies, making them vulnerable to physical attacks and setting up for Shatter. The formula for Frozen damage is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Execute this reaction by using a Cryo skill from Chongyun or Ganyu and then a Hydro skill from Mona or Xingqiu. Frozen is excellent for crowd control and pairing with a physical DPS to trigger Shatter for heavy damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;shatter-cryo--geo--cryo--anemo&#34;&gt;Shatter (Cryo + Geo / Cryo + Anemo)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shatter deals physical DMG and is triggered when Cryo hits an enemy affected by Geo or Anemo. The formula for Shatter is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Physical DMG+Physical DMG bonus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This reaction is best used with characters who deal significant physical damage. For example, use a Cryo attack from Kaeya followed by a Geo skill from Albedo or an Anemo ability from Sucrose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crystalize-geo--cryohydroelectropyro&#34;&gt;Crystalize (Geo + Cryo/Hydro/Electro/Pyro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crystalize generates a crystal that can be picked up to create an elemental shield. While it doesn&amp;rsquo;t deal direct damage, it provides an elemental barrier. The formula for the shield&amp;rsquo;s strength depends on the type of element and the character&amp;rsquo;s stats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To trigger Crystalize, use a Geo attack from Ningguang or Albedo and then hit an enemy with Cryo, Hydro, Electro, or Pyro. This reaction is ideal for teams that need a bit of extra defense, especially in high-damage encounters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;advanced-reactions&#34;&gt;Advanced Reactions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;burning-dendro--pyro&#34;&gt;Burning (Dendro + Pyro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burning deals Pyro DMG over time and is triggered by Dendro and Pyro interactions. The damage formula is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG+Pyro scaling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a consistent Burning reaction, use Dendro skills from Tighnari or Collei followed by Pyro attacks from Hu Tao or Klee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;quicken-dendro--electro&#34;&gt;Quicken (Dendro + Electro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quicken debuffs the target, reducing their resistance to reactions and setting the stage for Aggravate and Spread. This reaction is activated when Dendro hits an enemy that’s already affected by Electro. The formula is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To trigger Quicken, use Dendro abilities from Nahida and Electro abilities from Fischl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;aggravate-dendro--electro-after-quicken&#34;&gt;Aggravate (Dendro + Electro after Quicken)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aggravate boosts Electro DMG to enemies affected by Quicken. The formula for Aggravate is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG×1.15
For an Aggravate reaction, trigger Quicken and follow up with a strong Electro ability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spread-dendro--electro-after-quicken&#34;&gt;Spread (Dendro + Electro after Quicken)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spread increases Dendro DMG to affected enemies. The formula for Spread is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG×1.2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Execute Spread by using Dendro abilities followed by an Electro skill after triggering Quicken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;burgeon-dendro--hydro--pyro&#34;&gt;Burgeon (Dendro + Hydro + Pyro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burgeon creates a Pyro explosion that deals significant damage. The damage formula for Burgeon is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG×1.4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Burgeon, use Dendro abilities from Collei, Hydro from Xingqiu, and Pyro from Hu Tao for burst damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hyperbloom-dendro--electro--hydro&#34;&gt;Hyperbloom (Dendro + Electro + Hydro)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hyperbloom creates an Electro-infused bloom that deals AoE Electro DMG. The damage formula for Hyperbloom is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMG=Base DMG×1.5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To trigger Hyperbloom, start with Dendro and Hydro abilities, then follow up with an Electro attack for an explosive burst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;choosing-the-best-reactions-and-why&#34;&gt;Choosing the Best Reactions and Why&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to choosing the best reactions for your team, it depends on your playstyle and the characters you use. &lt;strong&gt;Melt&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Vaporize&lt;/strong&gt; are considered top-tier for their high damage output, especially when paired with Pyro or Hydro characters who can capitalize on their damage multipliers. &lt;strong&gt;Swirl&lt;/strong&gt; is invaluable for spreading elemental effects and setting up additional reactions, making&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it a staple in Anemo support teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Superconduct&lt;/strong&gt; is essential for teams that focus on physical damage, while &lt;strong&gt;Frozen&lt;/strong&gt; is perfect for crowd control, especially with physical DPS characters. Reactions like &lt;strong&gt;Electro-Charged&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Aggravate&lt;/strong&gt; are ideal for teams built around Electro, providing consistent and powerful bursts of damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the best reactions depend on your team composition. Choose reactions that complement your characters&amp;rsquo; strengths and maximize their damage potential, whether you’re looking for burst damage with &lt;strong&gt;Melt&lt;/strong&gt; or consistent pressure with &lt;strong&gt;Electro-Charged&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Understanding these reactions, their formulas, and their best usage scenarios will take your Genshin Impact gameplay to the next level. Master them, practice your rotations, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be well on your way to becoming an elemental reaction expert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Crusveder]&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. My Awesome First Blog CI/CD Pipeline</title>
      <link>/posts/blog-1-first-blog-cicd-pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog-1-first-blog-cicd-pipeline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; src=&#34;/images/crus-high-resolution-logo-transformed%201.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-blog&#34;&gt;Welcome to My Blog!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello there, and welcome to my corner of the internet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you stumbled in during a late-night browsing session or deliberately tracked this blog down (major kudos to you for that), I’m thrilled you’re here. This is a space where curiosity meets creativity—a digital lab, journal, and playground all in one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-this-blog-about&#34;&gt;What’s This Blog About?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At its heart, this blog is about exploration—of ideas, technologies, hobbies, and everything in between. I’ll be sharing insights from my personal and professional journey, diving deep into the topics that light me up and (hopefully) inspire you too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; src=&#34;/images/crus-high-resolution-logo-transformed%201.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-blog&#34;&gt;Welcome to My Blog!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello there, and welcome to my corner of the internet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you stumbled in during a late-night browsing session or deliberately tracked this blog down (major kudos to you for that), I’m thrilled you’re here. This is a space where curiosity meets creativity—a digital lab, journal, and playground all in one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-this-blog-about&#34;&gt;What’s This Blog About?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At its heart, this blog is about exploration—of ideas, technologies, hobbies, and everything in between. I’ll be sharing insights from my personal and professional journey, diving deep into the topics that light me up and (hopefully) inspire you too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s a glimpse at what you can expect:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learning Adventures:&lt;/strong&gt; As someone diving into fields like &lt;strong&gt;cybersecurity&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;machine learning (ML)&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;AI&lt;/strong&gt;, I’ll share practical tutorials and in-depth guides. Topics might include &lt;strong&gt;setting up secure workflows&lt;/strong&gt;, exploring &lt;strong&gt;neural network basics&lt;/strong&gt;, or dissecting real-world &lt;strong&gt;cybersecurity case studies.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Spotlights:&lt;/strong&gt; From coding a &lt;strong&gt;custom Wordle with Genshin Impact themes&lt;/strong&gt; to building a &lt;strong&gt;Spiral Abyss guide&lt;/strong&gt;, I’ll break down the process into actionable steps. Expect insights into technologies like Flask, Python, and front-end frameworks that make these projects possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaming Chronicles with a Twist:&lt;/strong&gt; While I’m a huge fan of &lt;strong&gt;Genshin Impact&lt;/strong&gt;, I also enjoy exploring how gaming intersects with technology. We’ll dive into the mechanics of &lt;strong&gt;game design&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;data analytics for team optimization&lt;/strong&gt;, and how to develop &lt;strong&gt;web tools&lt;/strong&gt; to enhance your gaming experience (imagine a tool to simulate Genshin team damage outputs!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guides and Tutorials:&lt;/strong&gt; Whether you’re navigating &lt;strong&gt;Obsidian for better productivity&lt;/strong&gt;, building a &lt;strong&gt;Python-powered AI summarizer&lt;/strong&gt;, or creating automation scripts for repetitive tasks, I’ll share step-by-step instructions and code snippets to make learning seamless.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; src=&#34;/images/Screenshot%202024-12-05%20175338.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-this-blog&#34;&gt;Why This Blog?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog isn’t just a diary—it’s a space to spark creativity, solve problems, and share ideas. It’s about connecting with like-minded folks who enjoy diving into the technical, creative, and geeky aspects of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe in breaking down complex topics into digestible insights, especially for beginners. Whether you’re just getting started with programming or exploring the intricacies of elemental reactions in &lt;strong&gt;Genshin Impact&lt;/strong&gt;, I’ve got you covered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lets-build-and-explore-together&#34;&gt;Let’s Build and Explore Together&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is just the beginning, and the journey ahead is wide open. I’ll be experimenting with content formats—blogs, tutorials, visuals, and maybe even interactive tools. Whatever helps bring ideas to life and makes learning fun and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any of this resonates, stick around! Engage with the content, leave comments, or suggest topics you’d like to see. This blog is a two-way street, and your input makes it all the better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, here’s to creativity, curiosity, and community. Let’s explore, learn, and create together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until next time,&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;[Crusveder]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Stay curious, stay persistent, and keep building. Great things happen when we embrace the process.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogs</title>
      <link>/titles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/titles/</guid>
      <description></description>
      <content></content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
